uei.com 2009-11-28

# Universal Electronics | About Us - Privacy Policy

  | 

**Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is important to Universal Electronics Inc. (UEI) and its subsidiaries. UEI provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our privacy policies and practices, including the types of information we may collect, why we collect it, how we use that information, and how you can exercise your choices as to how your information is used. This Privacy Statement is accessible from the bottom of each page of each UEI site to which it applies, and at every point where personal information is requested.  

**1\. Global Privacy Policy**  
UEI, with its subsidiaries, is a global company, with business operations and customers in many countries around the globe. UEI's intent is to comply with the privacy laws and regulations in all of the jurisdictions in which we conduct business, and our privacy practices are designed to provide protection for your personal information around the world. We may share your information within UEI and its subsidiaries, including transferring that information to countries in which we do business. Any UEI subsidiaries receiving your information will be governed by this Privacy Statement and are also bound by appropriate confidentiality and data transfer agreements. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where UEI or its subsidiaries are located. Your personal information is never shared outside UEI or its subsidiaries without your permission, except under conditions explained herein.  

**2\. Personal Information**  
Personal information is information that identifies an individual personally, including but not limited to name, address, phone number, e-mail address, personal characteristics, and financial information. You can visit many UEI Web sites without disclosing any personal information; however, in some instances, you will be required to provide personal information in order to complete a transaction or take advantage of the online resources made available by UEI.  
UEI will only collect the personal information reasonably necessary to accomplish the purpose for which it is collected, and will retain it only as long as is reasonably necessary. Personal information collected online by UEI may be combined with information you provide through other sources such as product registration, customer service call centers, or other methods.  

**3\. Tracking Technology**  
Like most Web sites, UEI’s Web sites may collect and log information automatically through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to you. Information collected may include items such as your IP address, the type and version of your browser, the length of time that you visit our site, search queries, your click-stream data, the location that referred you to our Web site and the average number of pages viewed. In addition, in order to improve our sites and your experiences with them, we may use "cookies" or other electronic means to track your visits. Cookies are simply small text files that  
our Web site can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online "shopping cart" to keep track of items you wish to purchase. Our site's server, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. Many consumers do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit most Web sites. Cookies cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites and they cannot infect your computer with viruses. If you want to know when this happens, or to prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a  
Web site attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer. Please click on the  
"Help" menu of your browser for information on setting your cookie preferences. You can also read more about cookies and how they work at various online sources, including [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).  

**4\. Children and Privacy**  
UEl is committed to protecting the online privacy of children. UEI does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from or about children under the age of 13, and UEI does not target its Web sites to children under 13.  
Additionally, UEI does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from or about children above the age of 13, without their parent's or guardian's consent. If UEI ever includes children above 13 as part of our intended Web site audience, those specific Web site pages will be clearly identified and provide an express privacy notice for children above 13, as well as processes to obtain parental approval and allow parental access to request removal of their children's personal information.  

**5\. How We Use Your Information**  
UEI collects personal information to enable us to provide products, services and information to our customers, potential customers, and business partners.  
We intend to let you know how we will use the information you provide before we collect it from you; and we intend to limit our use of that information to those purposes for which you give us permission. For example, UEI may collect financial information to facilitate the purchase of products or services online and postal or e-mail addresses to provide information in response to your request or to allow you to participate in promotions. We do not sell, trade or lease your information to others. UEI will not share your information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products, services or other UEI information. When we collect the information, we will obtain your consent regarding how you want or do not want us to use it. We may share your information with other persons or companies to help us manage our business.  
When we do so, we require them to use that information only for the purposes for which we provided it. We might use your information to develop aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, users, and site visitors, but these statistics will not include any personally identifiable information.  
**6\. Protecting Your Information**  
UEI uses procedural, manual and electronic security controls to maintain the confidentiality and integrity of personal information in our possession, and guard against its unauthorized access or use. We are responsible for providing an adequate level of protection for that information, and for limiting or granting access as required by applicable law. UEI employees may have access to your personal information as part of their job. Such employees are expected to keep that information in confidence and share it only with those UEI employees who have a business reason to know. Unauthorized disclosures or uses are strictly prohibited, and employees who violate our policies may be subject to disciplinary action.  

**7\. Communications from Us**  
If you provide us with your e-mail address, we may occasionally send you, in accordance with relevant regulations, e-mail with information or special offers about UEI products and services that may be of interest to you. We will give you opportunity to let us know if you want to receive such e-mail when you provide us your personal data or register for an online UEI promotion. This applies to promotional e-mail only, as UEI may find it necessary to e-mail you relating to your customer account or order. All promotional e-mail that you receive from UEI will tell you how to decline receiving future promotional email.  

**8\. Access to and Accuracy of Your Information**  
UEI strives to keep your personal information accurate. Where practical, we will provide you online access to your information and the ability to correct it. Otherwise, you can request access to your personal information by contacting UEI, as described below. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable precautions to verify your identity before granting access to your information. Certain areas of UEI's Web sites may limit access to users with a user id and password.  

**9\. Merger or Acquisition**  
UEI or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its assets could be acquired. If that should happen, UEI will make every reasonable effort to notify you in the event we share your information with the merging or acquiring entity to allow us to continue serving you.  

**10\. Links to Non- UEI Web Sites**  
UEI Web sites may provide links to third-party Web sites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the UEI Web site. UEI does not control those sites or their privacy practices, nor do we make any representations about third-party sites. Any information you provide to or through those sites is covered by the privacy policies of that site, not by this privacy statement. Please review the privacy policies of such sites before sharing your personal information.  

**11\. Disclosures Required by Law**  
Please be aware that in certain circumstances, UEI may be required by law to disclose your personal information. We will make every reasonable effort to limit the disclosure to only that information which is necessary to comply with such law.  
**12\. Employment Application Information**  
If you provide us your personal information in relation to an application for employment with UEI, we may use this information throughout UEI and its related entities for the purpose of consideration of your potential employment with UEI. Unless you instruct us otherwise, we will retain the information for future consideration.  

**13\. Contacting Us**  
If you wish to contact us about our privacy policies or to correct or delete information we may have about you, please send an e-mail to privacy@ueic.com, or send a letter to:

Universal Electronics Inc.  
Attn: Website Privacy  
6101 Gateway Drive  
Cypress, CA. 90630 USA

Please include your name, postal address, and e-mail address.

**14\. Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
UEI may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. If and when we do, we will post those changes to our Web site and update the revision date of this document, so you will always be aware of our privacy policies.  
Revision December, 2004
